<?xml version="1.0"?>
<VersionInfo>
    <VersionName>"3.0 'Iguazu'"</VersionName>
    <VersionNumber>"3.0.4"</VersionNumber>
    <DownloadLocation>"http://code.google.com/p/whitebox-geospatial-analysis-tools/downloads/list"</DownloadLocation>
    <Announcements number="6">
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2013-09-5</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Whitebox Version 3.0.4 has been released</Title>
            <Message><![CDATA[<p>This version includes the following updates:</p>
                    <ul>
                    <li>Improved support for scripting, including syntax highlighting and auto-completion.
                        There have been considerable improvements made to the Whitebox scripter.</li>
                    <li>Scripts can now be added as plugin tools, with integration in the tools panel.</li>
                    <li>Added Rename File tool, a Python script plugin.</li>
                    <li>Added Sink tool, a Python script plugin.</li>
                    <li>Added user-defined weights filter, a Groovy script plugin.</li>
                    <li>Added scripting examples in all 300+ plugin tool help files (this took quite a 
                        lot of time!).</li>
                    <li>The version of Jython (python for java) included in the library has been updated
                    to the stand alone version. This has increased the distribution size by 2 MB.</li>
                    <li>Added a quick-link to all displayed data layers in the file selection components
                    of tool dialogs.</li>
                </ul>]]>
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2013-07-18</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>How To Tutorials</Title>
            <Message><![CDATA[I'm working on a series of <i>How To</i> tutorials, which will be available 
                under the Tutorials tab of the Whitebox Help. For example, <i>How to create a new 
                tool</i>, <i>How to digitize new vectors</i>, and <i>How to get data into Whitebox</i>. 
                If you have any requests for other How To's please contact John Lindsay 
                (jlindsay@uoguelph.ca).]]>
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2013-06-24</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Translators Needed</Title>
            <Message>"We're working on improving Whitebox's support for multiple languages. You can help by volunteering as a translator.
                In the first phase of this work we have translated many of the user-interface labels, menus, and messages 
                into Persian, Greek, Chinese, German, Russian, Spanish, Catalan, Italian, and Polish thanks to the generous efforts of 
                numerous volunteers. In the second phase of this project, we would like to expand the number of supported languages 
                (Hindi, Arabic, Japanese, and Korean volunteers are especially needed, however any language would be appreciated) 
                and also translate the plugin tool names and descriptions. So there is still plenty of work ahead and any help that 
                you can provide would be greatly appreciated by the user community. If you are interested, please contact 
                Dr. John Lindsay (jlindsay@uoguelph.ca)."</Message>
        </Announcement>
    </Announcements>
</VersionInfo>
