<?xml version="1.0"?>
<VersionInfo>
    <VersionName>"3.2 'Iguazu'"</VersionName>
    <VersionNumber>"3.2.2"</VersionNumber>
    <DownloadLocation>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/download.shtml"</DownloadLocation>
    <DownloadArtifact>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/WhiteboxGAT.zip"</DownloadArtifact>
    <Announcements number="18">
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2015-04-12</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Whitebox 3.2.2 Has Been Released</Title>
            <Message><![CDATA[<p>The following additions/modifications have been made:</p>
<ul>
<li>LAS files can now be rendered based on the Classification, Scan Angle, and GPS Time
 in addition to Elevation and Intensity.</li>
<li>Added Conditional Evaluation tool (if-then-else statement).</li>
<li>Added a PickFromList tool, which outputs a raster with the value from a stack 
 of rasters based on an input position raster.</li>
<li>Added LowestPosition, HighestPosition, PercentEqualTo, PercentGreaterThan, and 
 PercentLessThan tools for working with raster stacks, i.e. lists of overlapping
 raster images.</li>
<li>Added a tool to create histograms based on the elevations, intensity, and 
 scan angles within a LiDAR (LAS) file. It will also output the percentiles of 
 the distribution, e.g. 95th percentile of elevation.</li>
<li>Added the AddPointCoordinateToTable tool, which can be used to add the x-y 
 coordinates of points within a Point type ShapeFile as fields within its 
 attribute table.</li>
<li>Added a tool to filter the points in a LiDAR (LAS) file based on a threshold 
 in the absolute scan angle.</li>
<li>The Merge Points Files tool was replaced with the more general Merge Shapefiles
 tool, which works with any ShapeType.</li>
<li>Added the FindLowestHighestLocations tool, which will output vector points 
 corresponding to the lowest and highest points in a raster.</li>
<li>Added ExtractRasterValuesAtPoints tool for extracting the cell values of each 
 image in a raster stack corresponding to a set of vector points. Values are 
 placed within the vector attribute table.</li>
<li>Added DeleteSmallLakesAndExtendRivers tool, which can be used to remove small 
 lakes (polygons) in a vector drainage network and to extend the associated river 
 network (intersecting polylines) into the interior of the lake.</li>
<li>Added a Long Profile From Point tool, which can generate one or more longitudinal
 profiles for the flowpaths issuing from a set of vector points.</li>
<li>Modified the Mosaic With Feathering tool to handle RGB images in addition to 
 continuous scale rasters. At the moment, this only works for the nearest-
 neighbour mode.</li>
<li>Added Image Stack Profile tool to create a line graphs for a set of vector points
 through an image stack, such as multi-spectral satellite image data.</li>
<li>Added a Simple Region Grow tool that will perform a very simple region grow 
 segmentation of pixels in an image stack based on a specified threshold.</li>
<li>Added parallel implementations of the D8 flow pointer and accumulation algorithms.</li>
<li>Fixed a bug in the Hillslopes tool.</li>
<li>I've added a whole suite of tools to the Elevation Residuals toolbox for 
 performing multi-scaled topographic position analysis. This includes modified 
 tools for calculating difference and deviation from mean elevations using an 
 integral image approach that is extremely computationally efficient, even with 
 large search windows. It also includes the Local Topographic Position Scale 
 Signature and the Maximum Elevation Deviation tools. Combined with the 
 'customRGBScript.groovy' script, these functions allow for the creation of
 some spectacular multi-scale topographic position visualizations. See:
 https://whiteboxgeospatial.wordpress.com/2014/12/25/a-new-form-of-multi-scale-topographic-position-visualization/
 for examples.</li>
</ul><]]>
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
    </Announcements>
</VersionInfo>
