<?xml version="1.0"?>
<VersionInfo>
    <VersionName>"3.2 'Iguazu'"</VersionName>
    <VersionNumber>"3.2.0"</VersionNumber>
    <DownloadLocation>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/download.shtml"</DownloadLocation>
    <DownloadArtifact>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/WhiteboxGAT.zip"</DownloadArtifact>
    <Announcements number="17">
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2014-05-04</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Whitebox 3.2.0 Has Been Released</Title>
            <Message><![CDATA[<p>The following additions/modifications have been made:</p>
<ul><li>Updated to Java 8. This is a major change and may result in some compatability issues.
 It will also mean that users will have to update their versions of Java to run
 Whitebox. Users will need to update their Java runtime to version 8 to run Whitebox.
 Please report any issues that you encounter as a result of this upgrade using
 Help -> Report An Error.</li>
<li>Added a ClusterAttribute tool that performs k-means clustering on a selected 
 group of attributes associated with a vector file.</li>
<li>Added zoom to selection for vector layers.</li>
<li>Added a Clip tool for vector clipping operations. I know, why has it taken this long?</li>
<li>Added floating point line thicknesses and changed the default line thickness to 0.75.
 This has greatly improved the cartographic output of Whitebox.</li>
<li>Added Export Table to CSV tool.</li>
<li>Added Hack Stream Ordering and Topological Stream Ordering tools.</li>
<li>Added Total Length of Upstream Channels tool.</li>
<li>Added Furtherest Upstream Channel Head Distance tool.</li>
<li>Added the Attribute Histogram tool for create histograms based on numeric data 
 contained in a shapefile's attribute table as well as the Attribute Scattergram tool.</li>
<li>Vectors can now be displayed with a palette rendered based on a boolean attribute.</li>
<li>Added palette nonlinearity for vectors with a scaled palette.</li>
<li>Fixed the raster-to-vector polygon conversion to include polygon holes.</li>
<li>Modified the minimum bounding box tool, and all related tools (e.g. elongation ratio,
 long axis, short axis) to use an analytical solution for finding the MBB.</li>
<li>Added a link to the Whitebox blog (http://whiteboxgeospatial.wordpress.com) in the help menu.</li>
<li>Added the Vector Attribute Gridding tool, which can be used to interpolate the spatial 
 pattern of average values of an attribute of vector features onto a raster grid. It
 essentially can be used to answer the question, of the vector features (points, lines, 
 or polygons) within the a local neighbourhood, what is the average value of some 
 attribute? This can be quite handy for visualizing patterns.</li>
<li>Added the Vector Feature Density tool, which is similar to the Vector Attribute Gridding 
 tool but works to map the spatial pattern of feature density (how many vector features 
 are within a local neighbourhood?).</li>
<li>Added the ability to rotate map titles. I know this isn't a proper labelling system
 yet, but I'm working on it. Hopefully map labels will be added this summer.</li>
</ul><]]>
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
    </Announcements>
</VersionInfo>
