<?xml version="1.0"?>
<VersionInfo>
    <VersionName>"3.2 'Iguazu'"</VersionName>
    <VersionNumber>"3.2.1"</VersionNumber>
    <DownloadLocation>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/download.shtml"</DownloadLocation>
    <DownloadArtifact>"http://www.uoguelph.ca/~hydrogeo/Whitebox/WhiteboxGAT.zip"</DownloadArtifact>
    <Announcements number="18">
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2014-05-04</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Whitebox 3.2.1 Has Been Released</Title>
            <Message><![CDATA[<p>The following additions/modifications have been made:</p>
<ul><li>Added the Retrieve SRTM DEM Data tool. This tool will download SRTM DEM tiles from
 the USGS FTP site, import the tiles into Whitebox GAT, and optionally fill 
 missing data holes and mosaic the tiles.</li>
<li>Added the ability to natively display LAS file point clouds in the map area.</li>
<li>Added Hex-binning tool.</li>
<li>Added a tool for isolating ground return points from LiDAR LAS files.</li>
<li>Added a tool for separating large LiDAR LAS files into smaller tiles of 
 shapefile points.</li>
<li>Added a Lee filter (Sigma filter) tool.</li>
<li>Added Interior Point tool.</li>
<li>Added CreateRectangularGridTool for creating a vector grid of polygons based on 
 a rectangular grid.</li>
<li>Added Single-part to Multi-part and Multi-part to Single-part tools.</li>
<li>Added List Unique Values tool to list all of the unique values in a categorical 
 field contained within a vector's attribute table. It will also report category
 frequency.</li>
<li>Added a fast depression breaching tool. Depression breaching is a far superior 
 method for pre-processing a DEM for hydrological analysis (e.g. mapping 
 watersheds). One of the reasons that people continue to fill depressions instead 
 of breaching is that filling is computationally much more efficient than 
 breaching. Well this tool is just about as fast as Whitebox's depression filling 
 tool. So now you have no excuse. This should be your default tool for hydrological
 processing of DEMs. Its result is not as good as the optimal breaching tool but
 it is far more efficient and still much better than filling. Please breach.</li>
<li>Added the tool BurnStreamAtRoads, which will carve a stream path through road
 embankments at the site of road/stream crossings.</li>
<li>Added a Minimum Interpolation tool for shapefile point inputs similar to the 
 Minimum Interpolation (LiDAR) tool.</li>
<li>Added the ability to update individual scripts from the source code repository. 
 This way, if you modify the code for a tool and break it, you can always 
 revert it back to the source on the main trunk. There's also now a menu entry 
 that will update all scripts for which there are newer versions within the 
 code repository and new scripts.</li>
<li>Added a Flood Order tool; details in tool's help.</li>
<li>Added a polygonize tool for converting polylines into polygons.</li>
<li>Updated the centroid (vector) tool with the option to handle multi-part polyline 
 and polygon features as a single entity or to extract centroids for each part, 
 as well as, the ability to extract centroids for groups of points.</li>
<li>Created a convenience tool, Feature Selection, for opening the feature selection 
 tab within the attribute table dialog after selecting a vector layer. If the 
 layer is not currently displayed, it will be. The reason I added this tool is 
 because many people search for feature selection in the toolbox rather than 
 in the attribute table dialog.</li>
<li>The Hillshade tool will now automatically calculate an appropriate z conversion 
 value when it detects that the DEM is in geographic coordinates with XY units 
 of degrees. I also fixed the Slope, Aspect, and all the Curvature tools to do 
 this as well.</li>
</ul><]]>
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
    </Announcements>
</VersionInfo>
