<?xml version="1.0"?>
<VersionInfo>
    <VersionName>"3.0 'Iguazu'"</VersionName>
    <VersionNumber>"3.0.2"</VersionNumber>
    <DownloadLocation>"http://code.google.com/p/whitebox-geospatial-analysis-tools/downloads/list"</DownloadLocation>
    <Announcements number="4">
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2013-06-27</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Whitebox 3.0.2 Now Available</Title>
            <Message>
                Whitebox 3.0.2 has been released for public use. It includes the following:
                
                    -Fixed a bug with the math tools that would not allow for a constant as the first operand.
                
                    -Added preliminary support for Catalan, Chinese (simplified and traditional), French, 
                        German, Italian, Polish, and Spanish. Thank you to the numerous volunteer translators 
                        (see 'About') that made this possible. We're still looking for volunteers to translate
                        to other languages and to help with the translation of the plugin tool names and 
                        descriptions.
                
                    -Added ability to import RGB GeoTiffs (I know you wanted this!) and fixed a number 
                        of bugs with this tool. There's still no support for compressed GeoTiffs.
                
                    -Added raster/vector conversion from geographic coordinates to UTM and vice versa.
                
                    -Added BalanceContrastEnhancement and DirectDecorrelationStretch tools.
            </Message>
        </Announcement>
        <Announcement>
            <Date>2013-06-24</Date>
            <Language>en</Language>
            <Title>Translators Needed</Title>
            <Message>"We're working on improving Whitebox's support for multiple languages. You can help by volunteering as a translator.
                In the first phase of this work we have translated many of the user-interface labels, menus, and messages 
                into Persian, Greek, Chinese, German, Russian, Spanish, Catalan, Italian, and Polish thanks to the generous efforts of 
                numerous volunteers. In the second phase of this project, we would like to expand the number of supported languages 
                (Hindi, Arabic, Japanese, and Korean volunteers are especially needed, however any language would be appreciated) 
                and also translate the plugin tool names and descriptions. So there is still plenty of work ahead and any help that 
                you can provide would be greatly appreciated by the user community. If you are interested, please contact 
                Dr. John Lindsay (jlindsay@uoguelph.ca)."</Message>
        </Announcement>
    </Announcements>
</VersionInfo>
